smartreviews.org 2018-05-11

# Smart Reviews

## Privacy

## Welcome to SmartReviews.org

Reading through and agreeing to our privacy policy is required before further use of this site. Here you can learn about whether we collect information, what we collect, how information is handled and more. Please check back and read this periodically as conditions of this policy may change. Changes to our policy are not made without advance notice on this page.

**Collection of Information**

We do not collect personal identifiable information from our users. Users might submit identifiable information when sending emails through our contact page, but we do not save this information on our servers. This is a free site with no membership requirements, so users should never be asked for personally identifiable information in exchange for website access. Please contact us if this ever appears to be the case. If we ever start collecting personally identifiable information, we will first provide notice and amend our privacy policy. Also, we don’t collect information on users to track their activity across the Web.

Even though we don’t collect personally identifiable information, user can still follow the opt out provision below and we’ll make sure to check for and remove information about them from our servers.

**Cookies**

This site uses cookies to learn how users interact with our site. Cookies are small files placed in your Web browser. You can instruct your browser to not accept cookies, but that might affect your experience with our website. Data from cookies allows us to view aggregate, non-personal data that can help us improve various aspects of the user experience. We do not use information from cookies to track, target or contact users.

**Third Party Links**

We reserve the right to host advertisements and links posted from advertisers or business partners. If you click one of these links and leave our site, please be aware these sites have their own privacy policies. You will need to read these statements to learn how these sites handle information.

**Information to Third Parties**

No information from our site—not even aggregate information—is ever distributed to third-party entities. We will only do this if requested by legal authorities and if said request is in accordance with the law.

**Our Security**

Our website is protected with updated security measures to defend against unauthorized access. Please report any suspicious posts, alerts or other issues through our contact page.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Changes to our privacy policy will be prominently displayed on this page.

**Opting Out**

Visitors can opt out of services to guarantee they will no longer be contacted by us. We destroy all personally identifiable information from those who opt out. To opt out, simply email optout@socialwisdomtoday.com with “OPT OUT” in the subject line.

**Contact Information**

Please contact us with any questions about this privacy policy.

Last Updated: Aug. 24, 2017
